<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jun Hahn</title>
    <link>https://junhahn.dev/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jun Hahn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://junhahn.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Started translation for a Golang Udemy course</title>
      <link>https://junhahn.dev/2018/go-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://junhahn.dev/2018/go-translation/</guid>
      <description>I started working as a contributor (translation Eng-Kor) for Google&amp;rsquo;s Go (golang) Programming Language, a Udemy course by Todd McLeod. Todd kindly accepted my suggestion to translate his contents in Korean and accepted my very first Pull Request.
The Github repository that I am working on is GoesToEleven/go-programming, espeically for English to Korean translation work.
I have researched some lectures/courses that seem good for a starting point to learn golang since I needed to pick a online course for a study group to learn golang (we decide to go through with a course with additonal materials) and Todd&amp;rsquo;s lectures on Udemy are highly recommended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joined Mercari Tech Conference 2018</title>
      <link>https://junhahn.dev/2018/mtc2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://junhahn.dev/2018/mtc2018/</guid>
      <description>Mercari Tech Conference 2018 at academyhills bldg., Roppongi, Minato, Tokyo
I joined Mercari Tech Conference 2018.
First, I thank to Mercari to offer free student ticket for the conference and a chance to have a lunch with their engineers and other participants.
I was able to have nice talks with some of my friends working there as well as other Mercari engineers with their current works. Even though I was trying to join most of session in general, I spent more time on some sessions that talked about Golang, Microservices, and somehow Machine Learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) on Ageing Soceity in East and North-East Asia (ENEA)</title>
      <link>https://junhahn.dev/2018/acmchi-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://junhahn.dev/2018/acmchi-article/</guid>
      <description>Jun Hahn, ACM SIGCHI Communication Ambassador
According to United Nations Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific (UN ESCAP), population ageing in East and North-East Asia (ENEA) is distinctly remarkable as the sub-region is home to a high ratio of elder people in the world [1]. In 2015, 32% of people in the world, older than 65 years old, are living in ENEA. In Asia, 56% of the older persons are from ENEA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://junhahn.dev/2018/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://junhahn.dev/2018/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hi, There? I am Jun, a master’s student at Department of Transdisciplinary Science and Engineering, School of Environment and Society, Tokyo Institute of Technology. communication ambassador of ACM SIGCHI.
Favourite quotes:
 The world is not a desktop. -Mark Weiser I propose to consider the question, &amp;lsquo;Can machines think?&amp;rsquo; -Alan Turing
 Computer science is no more about computers than astronomy is about telescopes. -Edsger Dijkstra
 Computer science inverts the normal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>